most Word documents are combined of text
however there are occasions where you
may wish to enhance the appearance of
the document make it look more
informative or more eye-catching and you
can do that by inserting tables charts
and images in this short video I'm going
to insert an image under chart just to
display information in a different way
and to personalize the letter to the
business so the first thing I'll do I'm
going to insert the company logo above
the address at the top of the letter
so what I need to do and ensure that the
cursor is blinking where I wish to
insert the image a good point to
remember us wherever your cursor is
blinking that is where it will import
the information or place the information
that you're putting into the document so
I've got that blinking just above the
address I will go to the insert tab I'll
select it's a picture and it's a picture
from file so it's a picture that I have
saved on the computer so I'll select
that and I'll save that under mate WP to
folder so I can just click on the
balloon image and that will insert the
image into the document now as you can
see the image is quite large and I can
reduce the size of it by clicking on the
little squares at the corner and I will
do that by the corner one because that
will keep the aspect ratio correct if I
reduced it in size using the side it
will compress the image exactly the same
if I did it via the bottom so I use the
corner and not shrinks the image and
keeps the aspect ratio correct so once
I'm satisfied and I'm happy with that so
then I've inserted the image so I'm
happy with that I could lower the
transparency I could do some artistic
effects there's various things you could
do once the image is in there and for
this one I'm just going to lure the
transparency a little just so it isn't
standing out as much so that's the lower
end ad so the next thing I'm going to do
is I'm going to import a chart just to
display the sales information for the
team and again I'll place the cursor
where I want to insert the chart and I
have the chart already set up in an
self spreadsheet and I've created the
chart using the sales information you
will learn more about this in the
spreadsheet unit so what I need to do is
I'm just going to highlight the chart as
you can see as soon as I highlight edit
it's telling me where it's drawing the
information from so I'll highlight that
and I'll use the command and see which
is now copied the chart if I place my
cursor there and then command + V it
will place the chart into the letter
good thing to remember is that is still
linked to the actual information now
there are the pierced options at the
bottom where in pierced as a picture
well as you can see I've got shot a link
to the Excel Theatre and the most
important thing about that is that means
that if I change the information in the
Excel spreadsheet it would update it
within the actual chart